<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brief on Indian News</title>
    <link>https://www.indiannews.live/tags/brief/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brief on Indian News</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 04:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.indiannews.live/tags/brief/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tamil Nadu CM Palaniswami to meet Prashant Kishor&#39;s I-PAC with an eye on 2021 state polls</title>
      <link>https://www.indiannews.live/news/c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.indiannews.live/news/c/</guid>
      <description>Chief Minister and AIADMK Co-coordinator Palaniswami left for Delhi on Friday evening.
Tamil Nadu Chief Minister Edappadi K Palaniswami is set to meet top executives of Prashant Kishor&amp;rsquo;s I-PAC on a possible consultancy for the 2021 state Assembly elections.
Palaniswami, who is also the co-coordinator of the ruling AIADMK, left for Delhi on Friday evening, with a top executive in I-PAC confirming that the meeting was scheduled for Saturday. The source however added that it was no indication that the poll consultancy firm will work for the AIADMK in the 2021 polls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today&#39;s hot news</title>
      <link>https://www.indiannews.live/news/b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 14:08:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.indiannews.live/news/b/</guid>
      <description>#Hello good boy
Pariatur ex anim ullamco labore ad laboris. Laboris ut irure mollit ullamco ex nostrud occaecat. Officia sint do deserunt officia. Voluptate dolore reprehenderit mollit sit commodo exercitation et in pariatur culpa. Dolor ad sunt dolore nostrud deserunt sunt. Proident commodo aliqua quis laboris esse laborum laborum aliquip cillum voluptate ipsum duis. Ipsum quis ad sunt aute consectetur excepteur ut dolore pariatur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>happy News</title>
      <link>https://www.indiannews.live/news/a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 16:41:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.indiannews.live/news/a/</guid>
      <description>#Hello sweet girl
news content goes here. Live news. real news. Live news. real news. Live news. real news. Live news. real news.
Live news. real news. Live news. real news. Live news. real news. Live news. real news. Live news. real news. Live news. real news. Live news. real news. Live news. real news. Live news. real news. Live news. real news. Live news. real news. Live news. real news.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>